//Questions for the Princess Quiz Storage
const STORE = [
    //Question 1
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the raccoon that follows Pocahontas?', 
        answers: [
            'Meeko', 'Bandit', 'Rocket', 'Kit'
        ], 
        correct: 'Meeko'
    }
    //Question 2
    {
        question: 'Which princess has a job (not including her Princess duties)?', 
        answers: [
            'Elsa', 'Cinderella', 'Tiana', 'Belle'
        ], 
        correct: 'Tiana'
    }
    //Question 3
    {
        question: 'Anna finishes the phrase "We finish each other\'s..." with?', 
        answers: [
            'Sentences', 'Sandwiches', 'Songs', 'Salads'
        ], 
        correct: 'Sandwiches'
    }
    //Question 4
    {
        question: 'What does the name Mulan mean?', 
        answers: [
            'Warrior', 'Chosen', 'Beautiful', 'Blossom'
        ], 
        correct: 'Blossom'
    }
    //Question 5
    {
        question: 'Which princess has brothers?', 
        answers: [
            'Moana', 'Merida', 'Snow White', 'Pocahontas'
        ], 
        correct: 'Merida'
    }
    //Question 6
    {
        question: 'Who is the first princess with powers?', 
        answers: [
            'Snow White', 'Elsa', 'Aurora', 'Rapunzel'
        ], 
        correct: 'Rapunzel'
    }
    //Question 7
    {
        question: 'This princess does not wear a dress.', 
        answers: [
            'Jasmine', 'Rapunzel', 'Tiana', 'Pocahontas'
        ], 
        correct: 'Jasmine'
    }
    //Question 8
    {
        question: 'Who is the youngest princess?', 
        answers: [
            'Anna', 'Jasmine', 'Snow White', 'Ariel'
        ], 
        correct: 'Snow White'
    }
    //Question 9
    {
        question: 'Which princess has violet eyes?', 
        answers: [
            'Tinkerbell', 'Belle', 'Aurora', 'Jasmine'
        ], 
        correct: 'Aurora'
    }
    //Question 10
    {
        question: 'What is the name of Belle\'s horse?', 
        answers: [
            'Philippe', 'Maximus', 'Khan', 'Samson'
        ], 
        correct: 'Philippe'
    }
    //Question 11
    {
        question: 'What is the Tinkerbell\'s sister\'s name?', 
        answers: [
            'Silvermist', 'Periwinkle', 'Fawn', 'Iridessa'
        ], 
        correct: 'Periwinkle'
    }
    //Question 12
    {
        question: 'What is the name of Cinderella\'s stepmother?', 
        answers: [
            'Olga', 'Narissa', 'Gothel', 'Tremaine'
        ], 
        correct: 'Tremaine'
    }
    //Question 13
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the giant snow monster Else created?', 
        answers: [
            'Snow', 'Marshmallow', 'Snowgie', 'Sentry'
        ], 
        correct: 'Marshmallow'
    }
    //Question 14
    {
        question: 'How many sisters does Ariel have?', 
        answers: [
            '7', '5', '8', '6'
        ], 
        correct: '6'
    }
    //Question 15
    {
        question: 'Which princess does not sing a song?', 
        answers: [
            'Aurora', 'Mulan', 'Merida', 'Snow White'
        ], 
        correct: 'Merida'
    }
];











